Get pitch slapped.
Pitch Perfect is a comedy, music, romance film directed by Jason Moore.
College student Beca knows she does not want to be part of a clique, but that's
exactly where she finds herself after arriving at her new school.
Thrust in among mean gals, nice gals and just plain weird gals, Beca finds that
the only thing they have in common is how well they sing together.
She takes the women of the group out of their comfort zone of traditional arrangements and into a world
of amazing harmonic combinations in a fight to the top of college music competitions.
Beca Mitchell, played by Anna Kendrick.
Aubrey Posen, played by Anna Camp.
Chloe Beale, played by Brittany Snow.
Jesse Swanson, played by Skylar Astin.
Fat Amy, played by Rebel Wilson.
Cynthia Rose, played by Ester Dean.
Pitch Perfect is a 2012 American musical comedy film
directed by Jason Moore and written by Kay Cannon.
It features an ensemble cast, including Anna Kendrick, Skylar Astin, Rebel Wilson, Adam DeVine, Anna Camp, Brittany Snow, Hana Mae Lee, Alexis Knapp,
Ester Dean, Kelley Jakle, Shelley Regner, Wanetah Walmsley, Ben Platt, Utkarsh Ambudkar, John Michael Higgins, and Elizabeth Banks.
The film's plot follows an all-female a cappella group that competes against an all-male group from
their own university to win the International Collegiate A Cappella Championship.
The film is loosely based on Mickey Rapkin's non-fiction book Pitch Perfect: The Quest for Collegiate a
Cappella Glory, and Moore's own experiences while attending Northwestern University.
Pitch Perfect premiered at the Cinerama Dome on September 24, 2012 and was
released in the United States by Universal Pictures on October 5, 2012.
It received generally positive reviews from critics and became a sleeper hit,
earning $115.4 million worldwide against a $17 million budget.
It was followed by two sequels, Pitch Perfect 2
(2015) and Pitch Perfect 3 (2017).
The film explores themes of competition, roommates,
college, female friendship, misfit.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.